But had a little We Shall Overcome on it.
Fight my battles.
I forget you can sing.
Sing something.
Just sing a little bit of that for me, please.
I would never attempt to sing a faith song for real, for real.
Well, just anything.
Well, since it's you.
Sing.
Why should I feel discouraged?
Why should the shadows come?
Why should my heart feel lonely and long for heaven and home?
When Jesus is my portion,
A constant friend is he
His eyes on the sparrow
And I know he watches me
I sing because I'm happy
I sing because I'm free
His eye is on the sparrow
And I know he watches
He watches, I know
Okay, okay
He watches me
This was not on my bingo card
For 2023.